that we really love and appreciate the
time that we've had with them.
>> It's a good sign for him, you know, and
we'll we'll continue to evaluate, but
he's done a really good job. He's made
his presence felt on teams. I think he's
played really well uh for those inside
backers. He's got a good understanding
of what we're trying to get done, the
intent of different things, and I've
been really pleased with him.
>> Yep. those guys, you know, they've
established themselves as guys we can
count on. You look at even last year,
you know, Queston Barry's been a guy
that has played at a high level, can
play right or left side. We're really
fortunate to have him. Justin Dedic and
Bo Liur did a great job of being able to
get a bunch of meaningful snaps last
year. They've continued to elevate their
game. They both those guys can play all
three interior spots. And I think Warren
McClennon's emergence and ascendance,
you know, to being a really good
football player where he can play right
tackle. We saw that on display last year
when Rob was missing. Um, and then I
think he's even doing a great job being
able to play on the left side as well.
So, good signs for those guys.
>> Yeah,
>> felt like it was good. You know, was
obviously challenged. That's a really
good defense. They played their lead
dogs and um, you know, we had a little
bit of trouble being able to get some
throws off, but he won on some routes
where he missed him earlier on and I
thought it was really cool for he and
um, you know, Dresser to be able to
connect on that vertical shot from the
slot. Um, wish he wasn't out of bounds
on that, but then it was cool to be able
to come back off the play action and be
able to make that play. You feel him.
He's just got a nice pace to his game.
Thought it was great to be able to get
him out there.
>> You know, I don't think so. I think, you
know, we had a couple guys going into
this game that were a little bit banged
up. AJ Green had a swollen knee. Ty
Hamilton wasn't feeling great. Wanted to
be smart with him. Um, Charles Woods
left with, you know, I think he's in the
concussion protocol. Um, but we'll see.
I mean, there's some of these guys, they
played their ass off today. And so,
hopefully we come out clean, Stew, and
we'll see. Uh, we'll see and I'll I'll
have updates for you as we go.
>> Yeah, I think really just Stson played
eight meaningful quarters. I thought he
did a great job. He got so many more
reps than he would have gotten otherwise
because Matthew was missing and um
thought we thought it was, you know, an
earned opportunity for Dresser and I was
really proud of him. And I thought as he
got into the flow of the game, I thought
he did an excellent job. And I thought,
you know, in the circumstances, Dave
Veron was outstanding. You know, he's
such a great job as a quarterback coach.
He's been a coordinator, can call plays
at a high level, and thought he did an
excellent job managing this situation
and putting our guys in a position to
make some plays today.
>> You good?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah, it was cool. We we talked about
it, but I'm I'm happy to answer it
again. It was uh really uh good to be
able to see him get out there, make some
plays. I thought he won on some routes
earlier where we just missed him. Came
back to the same sort of route in a man
coverage situation. It was kind of
perfect where it kind of was
underthrown. He's able to come back to
the football and that was a, you know,
good location on the ball based on the
coverage creates after the catch.
Thought that maybe was going to be a
touchdown. Foot was clearly out of
bounds and then comes back and makes a
good play. Thought he did a good job in
the run game and so he's a guy that
we're very excited about. I think really
Scooter Huff has done an outstanding job
with our tight ends. Mark Redmond did
some nice things today, but you look at
Tyler Higgby, Kobe Parkinson, Davis
Allen, Terrence Ferguson, you know,
that's a a group we feel really
fortunate to have.
>> It's it's really being able to identify
what's the best way to be able to put
this group together because there's
going to be a lot of guys that maybe
don't make our 53 that I think are NFL
53 caliber type of players. And that's a
positive problem for us and it's tough
for these guys because you love them.
You care about them so much. It's one of
the worst parts about this job is the
inevitability of of, you know, losing
some guys that that you really, you
know, start to develop meaningful
relationships with. That's what this is
about. Uh, but I do feel fortunate that,
you know, I look at it as we got 69 guys
on our football team with you. You know,
16 spots on the practice squad. And so,
there will be some really tough
decisions to be able to figure out what
are those 69 guys. Um, and we'll put our
heads together and try to make the best
decision for our team and be excited as
hell about starting our preparation for
the Texans.
>> Okay. Thank you guys.